(Sheldon:)Well... I'm responding to it.
(Leonard:)Uh, don't lower yourself
to their level.
(Sheldon:)Look, I am simply
(Sheldon:)going to defend our work,
scientist to scientist.
(Sheldon:)And failing that,
(Sheldon:)suggest that his mother enjoys
a string
(Sheldon:)of both human
and non-human lovers.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, my name's
on that paper, too.
(Leonard:)There's no upside to doing this.
(Sheldon:)He just left another comment.
(Raj:)What does it say?
"Upon review, I've
changed my mind about
"the Cooper-Hofstadter
hypothesis
"that space-time is like
a superfluid. In fact,
"it's inspired me to come up
with my own theory.
"Maybe space-time is like
two clowns
"with their heads in a bucket,
(Leonard:)much like Cooper
and Hofstadter."
(Sheldon:)Can I respond now?
(Sheldon:)Do it.
(Sheldon:)You mess with the bull,
you get the horns.
(Sheldon:)I'm about to show this guy
just how horny I can be.
(Leonard:)Somebody else do it.